Taking out the trash, one jerk at a time.
God Bless America is a comedy, drama, crime film directed by Bobcat Goldthwait.
Fed up with the cruelty and stupidity of American culture, an unlikely duo goes on a
killing spree, killing reality TV stars, bigots and others they find repugnant.
Frank, played by Joel Murray.
Roxy, played by Tara Lynne Barr.
Alison, played by Melinda Page Hamilton.
Ava, played by Mackenzie Brooke Smith.
Brad, played by Rich McDonald.
Chloe, played by Maddie Hasson.
God Bless America is a 2011 American black comedy film
written and directed by Bobcat Goldthwait.
Combining elements of political satire with dark humor, the film stars Joel Murray and Tara Lynne Barr as a middle-aged man and a teenage
girl who go on a killing spree after bonding over their disgust of what American culture has become in a post-9/11 world.
The film explores themes of mass murder, pop culture, social
commentary, killing spree, duringcreditsstinger.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.